<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>STREET SIDE</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on STREET SIDE</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Street Side&#39;s Mission</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2024-06-09-streetside-mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2024-06-09-streetside-mission/</guid>
      <description>Street Side Mission At Street Side, our mission is to celebrate and support the vibrant skateboarding culture by offering high-quality apparel that embodies the spirit of the streets. We believe that skateboarding is more than just a sport—it&amp;rsquo;s a lifestyle, an art form, and a community. Our goal is to provide skaters with gear that not only looks great but also performs under the toughest conditions. We are committed to sourcing sustainable materials and working with local artists to create unique, limited-edition designs that stand out in the skate park and on the streets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flake it till you make it</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2015-02-26-flake-it-till-you-make-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2015-02-26-flake-it-till-you-make-it/</guid>
      <description>Under what circumstances should we step off a path? When is it essential that we finish what we start? If I bought a bag of peanuts and had an allergic reaction, no one would fault me if I threw it out. If I ended a relationship with a woman who hit me, no one would say that I had a commitment problem. But if I walk away from a seemingly secure route because my soul has other ideas, I am a flake?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To be</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2015-02-13-hamlet-monologue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2015-02-13-hamlet-monologue/</guid>
      <description>To be, or not to be&amp;ndash;that is the question: Whether &amp;rsquo;tis nobler in the mind to suffer The slings and arrows of outrageous fortune Or to take arms against a sea of troubles And by opposing end them. To die, to sleep&amp;ndash; No more&amp;ndash;and by a sleep to say we end The heartache, and the thousand natural shocks That flesh is heir to. &amp;lsquo;Tis a consummation Devoutly to be wished. To die, to sleep&amp;ndash; To sleep&amp;ndash;perchance to dream: ay, there&amp;rsquo;s the rub, For in that sleep of death what dreams may come When we have shuffled off this mortal coil, Must give us pause.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dear diary</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2015-01-27-dear-diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2015-01-27-dear-diary/</guid>
      <description>What is it with that Mary girl? Dragging me to school every day. As if I had a choice. What you don&amp;rsquo;t hear in those nursery rhymes is that she starves me if I don&amp;rsquo;t go to school with her; it&amp;rsquo;s the only way I can stay alive! I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about being adopted by Little Bo Peep, sure I may get lost, but anything is better than being with Mary and those little brats at school (shudder, shudder).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/page/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Inigo Montoya. I have the following qualities:&#xA;I rock a great mustache I&amp;rsquo;m extremely loyal to my family What else do you need?&#xA;my history To be honest, I&amp;rsquo;m having some trouble remembering right now, so why don&amp;rsquo;t you just watch my movie and it will answer all your questions.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
