<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on STREET SIDE</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on STREET SIDE</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shred Diary</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2024-06-09-shred-diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2024-06-09-shred-diary/</guid>
      <description>What is it with that Mary girl? Dragging me to the skate park every day. As if I had a choice. What you don&amp;rsquo;t hear in those skate stories is that she leaves me behind if I don&amp;rsquo;t go to the park with her; it&amp;rsquo;s the only way I can keep skating! I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about joining Little Bo Peep&amp;rsquo;s crew—sure, I might get lost, but anything is better than being stuck with Mary and those little wannabe skaters at the park (kickflip, kickflip).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Street Side Mission</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2024-06-09-streetside-mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2024-06-09-streetside-mission/</guid>
      <description>Street Side Mission At Street Side, our mission is to celebrate and support the vibrant skateboarding culture by offering high-quality apparel that embodies the spirit of the streets. We believe that skateboarding is more than just a sport—it&amp;rsquo;s a lifestyle, an art form, and a community. Our goal is to provide skaters with gear that not only looks great but also performs under the toughest conditions. We are committed to sourcing sustainable materials and working with local artists to create unique, limited-edition designs that stand out in the skate park and on the streets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Shred</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2024-06-09-shred-or-not/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2024-06-09-shred-or-not/</guid>
      <description>To shred, or not to shred—that is the question: Whether &amp;rsquo;tis nobler in the mind to suffer The slams and bruises of outrageous fortune Or to take arms against a sea of troubles And by skating end them. To fall, to rest— No more—and by a rest to say we end The heartache, and the thousand natural shocks That skating is heir to. &amp;lsquo;Tis a consummation Devoutly to be wished. To fall, to rest— To rest—perchance to dream: ay, there&amp;rsquo;s the rub, For in that rest from skating what dreams may come When we have shuffled off this mortal coil, Must give us pause.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skate it Till You Make It</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2024-06-09-skate-it-till-you-make-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2024-06-09-skate-it-till-you-make-it/</guid>
      <description>Under what circumstances should we step off a path? When is it essential that we finish what we start? If I bought a skateboard that didn&amp;rsquo;t fit my style, no one would fault me for selling it. If I left a crew that disrespected me, no one would say that I had a commitment problem. But if I walk away from a seemingly promising skate route because my soul has other ideas, am I a flake?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
